The Anti-Zero-Zero defenses of Tundra Star are greater than we expected.
Even the ground forces are on strict alert.
With DES anti-forces controlling the airspace,
it's too risky to attempt an attack concert with the Flying Get.
The DES is as serious as our intel describes.
Subhata-san, we still want to do it!
I know. I will do everything it takes to find a plan
that will make the concert a success on this planet.
Woda forces in the area are doing what they can.
Leave it to us!
We're requesting cooperation from units in all areas.
We're currently searching for a low-security area to use for the concert.
Thank you.
I can't believe Mariko-sama expressed gratitude to us!
I'll put my life on the line this time!
After all, Mariko-sama, I...
Huh? Mariko-sama?
We'll wait here until the concert.
Main members of the concert should check their formations.
Under studies, get changed, do your makeup and start warming up. Now!
Okay!
Let's give it everything we have, girls!
Takamina, you should rest.
I can do it! Don't worry about me!
I'm not worried about you.
Concerts are once in a lifetime.
For some audience members, this may be their only opportunity to see Zero Zero perform.
Are you currently capable of putting on the best performance possible?
A performance that will stay with them for the rest of their lives?
Kanada!
Uh, yes!
You'll participate in the concert as Takamina's understudy.
You want… me to perform in her place?
Uh…
Ready and…
Let's go!
AKB0048!
ENGINE!
SH Februar
Love my dream
Flchodzi
I know
We'll be right back.
Hustle! Come on!
Yeah, sure.
I personally think that this mauve pink would suit you better, Megu.
Emori-san.
It's our first concert outside Akibasta, so I want you to look your best.
We've got to give it our all.
I don't care.
If I'm not performing with Yoko, it doesn't matter.
Who cares?
What?
I honestly wanted to become a successor with Yoko.
We were always together.
But now she's on the main stage, and I'm an understudy.
I'll probably be part of the combat team.
I never imagined we'd be so far from each other.
My dream was always to sing side-by-side with Yoko.
It's not any different from being with her, I swear.
Huh?
Through our hard work, we can make the successor's main concert shine even brighter!
As members, we're always connected.
We're always together.
Memori-san, I said terrible things to you and Kanada-san.
How can you ever be nice to...
Don't worry about it.
After all, I'm a huge masochist!
What?
Let's have some fun!
Okay!
Kanada, you need to move by 0.75.
Got it!
Left foot first?
What good does it do just to change position?
Think of how it looks!
Oh!
Yoko's so scary!
It's tough love.
It's just supposed to be a formation check, though.
I think Kanada's dancing pretty well.
Yoko-san.
I'm sorry!
This girl really is amazing.
Is it time yet?
Makoto-san, your makeup is coming off again.
I practice too much!
A snowman!
What's wrong?
I want to make a big snowman.
You come from a desert planet, don't you?
Is this your first time seeing snow?
Snowman!
Hey, it seems like it'll be a while.
Why don't we go outside for a bit?
What?
Don't you think that's a bad idea?
The DES might be out there, you know.
Why would they care?
No one knows about us.
We're just trainees.
We'll call it reconnaissance.
Uh, Jerry?
Snid!
Hey, I'm going to eat!
Mm-hmm.
Do you want to tag along with them, Magu?
Uh, yeah.
Oh.
Those girls.
They're hopeless.
Oh.
Hooray, it's snow, snow, snow!
Sonura, are you okay?
Oh, my.
It doesn't hurt.
Daddy, what are you looking at?
That.
Huh?
Oh, it's a town.
Holy smokes.
What a gloomy place.
That old man doesn't have any energy.
I wonder if it's because of the gray skies.
Hey, you guys.
Doesn't this place remind you of Lancaster?
Yeah, you're right.
It brings back memories.
Oh.
What are all these people lined up for?
Are they distributing supplies?
They seem to be handing out bread over there.
I'm going to get some food.
You're not supposed to do that, Sanity.
Those supplies are for people around this town who really need them.
Oh, right.
These people seem really down on their luck.
It's really kind of sad.
They don't have any energy.
Yeah.
It's like even their hearts are frozen.
These are the people of a planet with a total entertainment ban.
I wonder if it's a good idea to perform a concert on this planet.
Huh?
Once the concert ends, they'll go back to their regular entertainment ban.
It's like giving them dreams, only to take them away.
When you think about it, she's kind of right.
But...
But I still want them to see a Zero Zero concert!
Huh?
Heavy rotation?
Oh, it's a group of little girls!
We don't mean to do any harm!
It's the seventy-seventh!
There's even seventy-fifth generation anymore and seventy-sixth generation with Gooby, too!
Do you recognize us?
You know who we are?
Yes, of course!
What in the...
This!
It's our promotional video!
That's right!
I'm so happy! I heard the Zero Zero concert had been cancelled!
Getting to meet you in person is like a dream!
A dream?
Are you going to come see our concert this evening?
Yeah! I even begged my mom to let me see it tonight!
I saved up all my allowance!
Yeah, and I helped out a lot, too!
What good girls!
She called us good girls!
I did some more, too!
Yeah, I see!
They're just like we were when we were little!
That's right!
Our dream was born under those grey skies!
They're just like we were!
Awwagh!
Alright!
Dun-Dun-Dun-Dun-Dun-Dun-Dun!
I have missed you, I have missed you!
I have missed you!
Yeah!
I have missed you, I have missed you!
I have missed you!
Yeah!
All my life!
Agisa?
I'll sing, too!
I chose things, was it...
As fast as it will go
Go to you
No more secrets
No fake files
That's one way to do it
Find something and no longer say no
All I could think of was whether or not it was a good idea to perform a concert here
But Nagisa was different
Kira!
I know they are not gone
If your heart is where I belong
I know life must be
What are you doing?
Are you members of Zero Zero?
These girls have nothing to do with this
Throw down your weapons!
Hey!
Get out of here!
Put me down right now!
Girl, can you hear me?
It's Sabasa-san
I like what you're doing
Huh?
Our new plan of attack will be multiple simultaneous concerts
Simultaneous concerts?
Huh?
Is that Zero Zero?
Is that Zero Zero…
どうしちゃったんだろう?
私知らぬ間に
コーリー落ちてた
何がきっかけだったの?
They're behind us!
入り口も思い出せないのよ
What?
ハートがったウイルスに
誰か知らぬ間にさ
どんな注射も聞かないわ
あなたのことばかり
The Understudy's Simultaneous Concerts
have scattered the DES.
We'll use this opportunity
to launch the concert.
This simply can't be.
Huh?
That's what I had thought.
But I seem to be...
in love with you, everyone!
Damn, idols!
This is fantastic!
The DES soldiers are scattering!
Come in!
Subasa-san,
the fans we summoned
to the main venue are assembling.
We're ready when you are.
Showtime in ten minutes!
Roger that!
Our first song is River!
Alright!
You're close.
Thanks!
This is...
Do your best for Takamina.
I may not be good enough to replace Takamina-san,
but I'm sure I can do my best.
I'll make you proud Takamina-san.
Got him!
Zero-Zero ran this way!
They're over there!
What?!
Ha-
They're over there.
Get out and arms.
Now we're mobbing these lights,
a-
Are you in love?
I know有人's mind is a whisper in the짝복,
We're only in love.
And they can't go in love and I hate
But I'm not walking around where we're geected...
It's a little tight, but putting on these clothes and feeling like Takamina-san makes me feel like I can do anything.
Let's go!
Okay!
Wait!
Takamina!
Takamina-san!
You shouldn't be up now! You need to rest!
I'm fine now.
Take it off!
What?
Those are my clothes.
I'm performing in the concert!
Takamina!
Let me go on! I promise I won't make a fool of myself!
As a fifth generation Takamina, I'll give the people of this planet the greatest concert of their lives!
Very well. Get ready in two minutes.
Thank you very much!
Uh...
Kanina...
Yeah...
Wow! Look at all these people!
It's just like the girls said!
Huh?
I'm so excited!
The main performance is starry. Continue drawing the DES away in small groups. And be careful.
Huh?
Currently, Chieri, Nagasa, Orane, and Yuka are all in that area.
What?
The four of us have a position to put on a concert!
Nagasa, Orane...
Nagasa!
Ak..V...
Oh!
Wow love you
Mm
Why am I?
Man driver
How do you feel
I keep your dreams
due to origin
I can't feel about fromWhy
I feel all walking
Let's go! Yeah!
Let's go!
Oh, no.
Yeah!
I knew it. He really is cool.
This really is cool.
Ah!
This is good!
In a small town, under gray skies, a dream was born.
The four of us want to join Zero-Zero together.
The big dream of four little girls.
Now the four of us are making that dream come true in some small, small way.
Now on.
10ヶ月
辛かった
あのレッスンを
共に過ごして気づいた
仲間はいつだってここにいる
私は一人きりではないんだ
一緒に あの星を見ている
みんながいること 支えだった
小人なりと 壁にしている
お客さんもめ、 本船にしてくれ
さあ Targetaに relation
だから食欲を 気付けたい
But there's the encore!
What?
Takamina-san!
You idiot!
Have a little more faith in your friends!
I'm going now!
But...
I had no idea you were barely hanging in there.
You looked great on stage tonight.
Okay, girls!
Let's go out there and give them a great encore for Takamina!
Yeah!
It was amazing.
It was a fantastic performance.
Kaneda...
I don't deserve to wear your clothes yet, Takamina-san.
But I'll do my best.
Someday, I'm gonna catch up to you big time!
I can't let you catch up to me that easily.
What?
I know she must have been frustrated.
But no matter how hurt she is...
A member of Zero Zero always puts the concert first.
Takahashi Minami.
The name Takamina is...
Is...
Best suited to her.
To Kaneda.
We've set up a gravure photo shoot for this weekend.
Oh, I can smell the ocean!
My breath!
What's going on, Buddha?
Are you dying?!
In that case...
I shall help you.
Who?
Bye!
What's going on...
Do not know...
It's...
It's great.
It'suckle Voyager.
Watch this!
Not one need to have any tape out.
What?
The holy smoke